know i didn't just see videos of folks in jamaica americans black americans in jamaica
post hurricane melissa complaining about the food they were provided by the hotel what are y'all
doing for gas you all know this phone was coming right so you gonna give us bag lunches we'll go
anywhere in the united states we just need to get out of jamaica please we'll increase your
okay this is a lunchbox post hurricane hurricane melissa one of the most severe hurricanes
to hit the region ever no you know what i couldn't i couldn't have seen that because that
because that would be utterly insane disgraceful and ungrateful as somebody who has actually been
in the caribbean at a hotel during a hurricane it's very very scary i was in hurricane barrel
while at mount cinnamon hotel in grenada last year i need to remind some of you that these people are
literally with your instead of with their families during severe weather event
that could affect and impact their lives and their livelihood and you're talking about what
they're literally there putting together meals with whatever they have to get to you i remember
that folks at mount cinnamon was coming through while the wind was moving on crazy and everything
making sure that we had something to eat oh you're damn rude i had heard that this was happening and i just
assumed it was white folks i just was like yeah that that tracks and this is why we continue to have
dissension amongst the diaspora because so often folks go other places and act a mess
and there's a version of this that is done by african folks there's a version of this but that is done
by caribbean folks and there is a version of this that is done by american folks and everybody needs to
stop showing up in other places acting like the colonizers that colonize them cut it out
stop showing up in the arms